<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="73">

    <author>Bjoern_aka_FactoryMODS</author>



             
    <version>1.6.0.0</version>
	
    <title>
        <en>LogisticWarehouse</en>
        <de>LogistikZentrum</de>
    </title>
	
    <description>
        <en>
<![CDATA[logistics center
Price: 650000 €
Maintenance: 150 €

Function: The logistics center is used to store all standard products. The camp is divided into 4 parts.
Transhipment point: This is where the goods can be accepted and loaded. All gates can be opened and closed with a switch.
Main warehouse: Most products can be found here, e.g. flour, sugar, fabrics, etc.
Cold storage: Here you can store products such as Tomatoes, lettuce, chocolate, etc. The cold store has 2 more doors where you can store directly from there.
Small warehouse: Here you will find storage space for e.g. Empty pallets, wool etc.
All goods that are stored are also displayed visibly on the shelves from a certain quantity, and all shelves are equipped with displays that show the current level. 

All production and the logistics center are based on the Revamp Mod Script]]>
        </en>
        <de>
<![CDATA[Logistikzentrum
Preis: 650000 €
Unterhalt: 150 €

Funktion: Das Logistikzentrum dient zum einlagern aller Standard Produkte . Das Lager ist in 4 Teilen geteilt.
Umschlagsplatz: Hier können die Waren angenommen und Verladen werden. Alle Tore können per Schalter geöffnet und Geschlossen werden.
Hauptlager: Hier finden die meisten Produkte platz wie zb. Mehl, Zucker, Stoffe usw.
Kühllager: Hier kannst du Produkte Lagern wie zb. Tomaten, Salat, Schokolade usw. Das Kühlager hat nochmal 2 Tore wo man dann direkt von da einlagern kann.
Kleines Lager: Hier findest du Lagerplatz für zb. Leerpaletten, Wolle usw.
Alle Waren die eingelagert werden werde ab einer bestimmten menge auch sichtbar in den regalen angezeigt, zudem sind alle Regale mit Displays ausgestattet die den aktuellen Füllstand anzeigen. 

Alle Produktion sowie das Logistikzentrum basieren auf da Revamp Mod Script]]>
        </de>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>icon_Logistikzentrum.dds</iconFilename>


    <brands>
        <brand name="FACTORYMODS" title="FactoryMODS" image="Brand_FactoryMODS.dds"/>
    </brands>


    <multiplayer supported="true" />

    <storeItems>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="Logistikzentrum.xml"/>
	
    </storeItems>
	
	<extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/revamp_check.lua" />  
		<sourceFile filename="scripts/addplaceablecategory.lua" />
	</extraSourceFiles>

    <fillTypes filename="fillTypes.xml"/>


    <dependencies>
        <dependency>FS22_A_ProductionRevamp</dependency>
   </dependencies>
   <revamp minVersion="1.2.0.8">                                     
   </revamp> 
	  
   <l10n filenamePrefix="XML/translation"/> 




	
</modDesc>
